punchjump.com 2011-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Punch Jump

**Privacy Policy**

Security

Punch Jump L.L.C employs security measures to keep personally identifiable data safe from unauthorized access, alteration, or destruction. We take administrative and technical actions to prevent data loss, unauthorized access and misuse, but make no guarantee to full data protection at any time.

Information collection

Punch Jump L.L.C collects personally identifiable information from registered users and anonymous, aggregate information from all users. We use cookies to identify your IP address, browser and track site travel. A cookie is a small file sent to a user’s computer to record general user information or activity. Users can choose to disable the receipt of cookies, though certain site features may not be accessible without cookies enabled. The information we collect is used to send opt-in materials, make site content more relevant to readers, and measure site usage.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Shared information

Punch Jump L.L.C will not rent or sell any personally identifiable information to third-parties without your consent, and will not divulge personal information unless required to by law. We may share aggregate, anonymous information and personal information (i.e., name and address) to third-parties or affiliates participating in promotional campaigns including, but not limited to, sweepstakes, contests, promotions, and sponsorships.

Registered members have the choice to opt-in to receive marketing material from third-parties and share personal information submitted through the registration process. Members who opt-in to receive marketing materials may have personal information shared with third parties. Members who choose to opt-out will not have information shared or receive any marketing material from third-parties.

Links

The Punch Jump website contains links or advertisements that lead to third-party areas outside our site. We are not responsible for content outside the Punch Jump site. These websites may have different privacy policies and data gathering practices that affect you. Please check their privacy policies for more details.

Children’s Privacy

Punch Jump L.L.C services are not directed at to children under the age of 13. We are in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Children under 13 are not allowed to register as a member of Punch Jump. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any children under the age of 13.
